Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University Office of the President Records 1986-2000
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University Office of the President Records
1986-2000
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
UA2000-41
Washington State University. Office of the President
22.5 Linear feet of shelf space 24 Boxes
Administrative and financial files related to the WSU President's Office from 1993-1998, in which Sam Smith was the presiding president.
The president is the chief executive officer of the multi-campus Washington State University system and reports to a 10-member Board of Regents.
As the University’s leader, the president collaborates with a wide range of internal and external stakeholders to define the vision and set the direction for the institution. As the champion of its reputation, the president articulates the strategic goals and messages of the University in order to build broad support for and ownership of WSU’s aspirations among its many constituents, including faculty, staff, students, alumni, the Board of Regents, the WSU Foundation, local communities, government, business, and industry leaders statewide, the media, and the general public. Samuel (Sam) H. Smith was selected by the Board of Regents on March 7, 1985, to serve as the institution’s 8th president. He took office at age 45 on July 1, 1985, and served for 15 years.
Mostly administrative and financial files related to the WSU's Presidential Office during Sam Smith's time as president from 1993-1998.
This is an unprocessed collection. Any arrangement reflects either a pre-existing order from the records' creators or previous custodians, or preliminary sorting performed by staff.
All boxes contain administrative files and correspondence related to the WSU President's Office. Boxes 1-9 contain files from 1993 and are organized by alphabet and subject matter. Boxes 10-17 contain files from 1994 and are filed by alphabet and subject order. Boxes 18-24 contain files from 1995-1998 and are filed by alphabet, date, and subject order.
This collection is open and available for research use.
This material was transferred to WSU Libraries' MASC by Linda Commons of the President's Office on December 29, 2000 and retained as UA2000-41.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. Office of the President -- Records and correspondence
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- 1993
  - A-C
    - Files Index, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous "A", Jan.-Mar. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous "A", Apr.-June 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous "A", July-Dec. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American Council on Education (ACE), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Admissions, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Association of Governing Boards (AGB), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, College of, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture Cooperative Ext. Service, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Agriculture Research, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Association, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Applications (A-M), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Applications (N-Z), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Art Museum, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Associated Western Universities, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - ASWSU, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Athletics, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Attorney, WSU, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous "B", 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Baseball, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Basketball, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Battelle Pacific Northwest Laboratory Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bhatia Lecture, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Boeing, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Boy Scouts, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Budget Office, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Business Affairs, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Business and Economics, College of, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous "C", Jan.-March 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous "C", Apr.-June 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous "C", July-Dec. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Case, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Center for Human Rights, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Chamber of Commerce- Pullman, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - C-D
    - Chamber of Commerce- Spokane, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - China, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - CIR Communications Infrastructure, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - College Board, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Committees (Senate)- Academic Affairs, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Committees (Senate)- Building Names, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Committees (Senate) A-M -Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Communications, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Complaints A-F, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Complaints G-L, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Complaints M-R, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Complaints S-Z, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Complaints: Budget, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Complaints: Crimson Company, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Complaints: Environment and Recycling, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Complaints: Layoffs, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Congratulations, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Compliments, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Condolences, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Conferences and Institutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Contracts A-M, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Contracts N-Z, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Consortium for International Development (CID), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Council of Presidents (COP), Jan.-June 1993 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Council of Presidents (COP), July-Dec. 1993 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Council on Competitiveness, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous "D", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Degrees, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Development Campaign Project, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - D-F
    - Development Foundation, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Development Gift Reports, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Development Office Letters Signed by SHS (1), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Development Office Letters Signed by SHS (2), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Development Office Letters Signed by SHS (3), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Development Office Letters Signed by SHS (4), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Development Office Letters Signed by SHS (5), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Development Office, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Development: President's Associates, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Distance Education, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Distance Education (2), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Diversity, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Dow, Lohnes & Albertson, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Miscellaneous "E", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - College of Education, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Engineers and Architects, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Executive Budget Committee, Jan.-Apr. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Executive Budget Committee, May-Dec. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Extended University Services, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Miscellaneous "F", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Facilities Planning, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Faculty Manual, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Faculty Senate, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - F-K
    - Federal Relations, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Financial Aid, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Financial Info: Tuition and Fees, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Football, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Forward Washington, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Miscellaneous "G", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Golden Key, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Government Relations, Jan.-June 1993 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Government Relations, July-Dec. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - GPSA, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Graduate School: OGRD, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Grapevine, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Miscellaneous "H", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Honors Program, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Honor Roll, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Administration (HRA), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Human Relations and Resources, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Miscellaneous "I", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - IBM, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Inaugurations, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - International Programs Development Office, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Invitations, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Idaho Research Foundation, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Miscellaneous "J", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Japan, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Joint Center for Higher Education, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Joint Center for Higher Education, July-Dec. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Miscellaneous "K" (1), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Miscellaneous "K" (2), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - K-N
    - Kitchen Cabinet, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Miscellaneous "L", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Leadership Conference, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Libraries, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Miscellaneous "M", Jan.-June 1993 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Miscellaneous "M", July-Dec. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Military Science: Aerospace, Military, Naval, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Minority Affairs, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Morrison, Sid, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Murrow Symposium, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Music, Department of, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Miscellaneous "N" (1), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Miscellaneous "N" (2), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), Jan.-June 1993 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - NCAA, July-Dec. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - National Extension Leadership Development Program, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), Jan.-Apr. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - NASULGC, May-Aug. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - NASULGC, Sept.-Dec. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - NASULGC- Commission on Information Technology Education, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Telecommunications Board, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - New Student Orientation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - News and Information: Clippings, May-July 1993 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - News and Information: Clippings, Aug.-Sept. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - News and Information: Clippings, Oct. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - News and Information: Clippings, Nov.-Dec. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - N-R
    - News and Information: Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - News and Information, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - News and Information: News Releases, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Nominations, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Northwest Association of Schools and Colleges, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Miscellaneous "O", 1993 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Miscellaneous "P", 1993 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Pac-10 Conference, Jan.-Mar. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Pac-10 Conference, Apr.-June 1993 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Pac-10 Conference, July-Sept. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Pac-10 Conference, Oct.-Dec. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Parking, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Physical Plant, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Plant Pathology, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Police Department, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - President: House, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Professional Leaves, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - Provost, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - Pullman, City of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - Pullman 2000, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - Miscellaneous "Q", 1993 (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - Questionnaires, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - Reconfiguration, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - Miscellaneous "R", 1993 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - Recommendation (A-M), 1993 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - R-S
    - Recommendation (N-Z), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - Registrar, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - Retirements, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - Research and Technology Park, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - Residence Life and Housing, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Russia, Jan.-June 1993 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - Russia, July-Dec. 1993 (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - Russia (Extra Manuals), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - Miscellaneous "S", Jan.-June 1993 (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - Miscellaneous "S", July-Dec. 1993 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - Miscellaneous "S", (2) Jan.-June 1993 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - Scholarships, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - Sciences and Arts, College of, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - Spokane Intercollegiate Research and Technology Institute, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - Small Business Development Center, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - Spokane, City of, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - Spokane, Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - Spokane Symphony, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - Spokane Unlimited, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - Staff Senate, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 187)
    - State Legislature (1), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - State Legislature (2), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 189)
    - State Legislature (3), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - State Attorney General, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 191)
    - State Auditor, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 192)
    - State: Combined Fund Drive, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 193)
    - State Ecology, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 194)
    - State: General Administration, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 195)
    - State Governor (1), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 196)
    - State Governor (2), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - S-U
    - State: Higher Education Coordinating Board, Jan.-Feb. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 198)
    - State: HECB, Mar. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 199)
    - State: HECB, Apr.-May 1993 (Box 8, Folder 200)
    - State: HECB, June, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 201)
    - State: HECB, July-Aug. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 202)
    - State: HECB, Sept.-Oct. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 203)
    - State: HECB, Nov.-Dec. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 204)
    - State: Higher Education Personnel Board, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 205)
    - State: Information Sciences, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - State: Legislature, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 207)
    - State: Liquor Control Board, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 208)
    - State: Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 209)
    - State: Office of Fiscal Management, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 210)
    - State: Senators and Representatives, Jan.-June 1993 (Box 8, Folder 211)
    - State: Senators and Representatives, July-Dec. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - State: Trade and Economic Development, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - Student Affairs, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Miscellaneous "T", 1993 (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - Thank You, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, College Retirement Equities Fund, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Track, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - Tri-Cities: Commercialization Task Force, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - Miscellaneous "U", 1993 (Box 8, Folder 220)
    - United States: Agriculture, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 221)
    - United States: Defense, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - United States: Education, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - United States: Energy, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - United States: Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 225)
  - U-Z
    - United States: Senators and Representatives, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 226)
    - Universities and Colleges: Central, Eastern, Evergreen, Western, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 227)
    - Universities and Colleges: Idaho, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 228)
    - Universities and Colleges: Miscellaneous A-I, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 229)
    - Universities and Colleges: Miscellaneous J-R, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 230)
    - Universities and Colleges: Miscellaneous S-Z, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 231)
    - Universities and Colleges: University of Washington, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 232)
    - US Bank, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 233)
    - US West, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 234)
    - Miscellaneous "V", 1993 (Box 9, Folder 235)
    - Veterinary Medicine, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 236)
    - Vice President: Business Affairs, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 237)
    - Washington Agriculture and Forestry Leadership, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 238)
    - Vice-Provost: Extended University Sciences, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 239)
    - Vice Provost: Human Relations and Resources, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 240)
    - Vice Provost: Research and Dean of Graduate School, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 241)
    - Volleyball, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 242)
    - Miscellaneous "W", Jan.-June 1993 (Box 9, Folder 243)
    - Miscellaneous "W", July-Dec. 1993 (Box 9, Folder 244)
    - Washington State Campus Compact, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 245)
    - Washington State 4-H, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 246)
    - Washington Water Power, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 247)
    - Water Research Center, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - Washington Council for International Trade, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 249)
    - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 250)
    - Women, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 251)
    - Women's Resource and Research Center, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - Washington State China Relations Council, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 253)
    - WSU Spokane, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - WSU- Tri Cities, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - WSU Vancouver, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 256)
    - YMCA and YWCA, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 257)
    - Miscellaneous "X", 1993 (Box 9, Folder 258)
    - Miscellaneous "Y", 1993 (Box 9, Folder 259)
    - Miscellaneous "Z", 1993 (Box 9, Folder 260)
- 1994
  - A-C
    - Files Index, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 261)
    - Miscellaneous "A", Jan.-June 1994 (Box 10, Folder 262)
    - Miscellaneous "A", July-Dec. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 263)
    - Admissions, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 264)
    - Agriculture: College of, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 265)
    - Agriculture, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 266)
    - Agriculture: Research, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 267)
    - Alumni Association, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 268)
    - American Council on Education, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 269)
    - Applications (A-M), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 270)
    - Applications (N-Z), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 271)
    - Art Museum, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 272)
    - Association Governing Boards, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - Association for Faculty Women, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - Associated Western Universities (AWU), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - AWU 2, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - ASWSU, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 277)
    - Athletics, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - Attorney, WSU, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - Miscellaneous "B", 1994 (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - Baseball, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 281)
    - Basketball, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 282)
    - Battelle, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 283)
    - Battelle PNL ADV. Committee/Battelle, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 284)
    - Bhatia Lecture, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 285)
    - Biochemistry, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 286)
    - Blethen, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - Boeing, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - Black Male Orientation to Leadership Development (BOLD), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 289)
    - Boy Scouts, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 290)
    - Budget Office, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 291)
    - Business Affairs, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 292)
    - Business and Economics, College of, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 293)
    - Miscellaneous "C", 1994 (Box 10, Folder 294)
    - Campus Compact, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 295)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 296)
    - Chile, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 297)
    - China, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 298)
    - Clippings, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 299)
    - College Board, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 300)
    - Communications, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 301)
    - Complaints (A-F), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 302)
  - C-D
    - Complaints (G-P), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 303)
    - Complaints (R-Z), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 304)
    - Complaints: Budget, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Complaints: Environment and Recycling, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - Compliments, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - Consortium for International Development (CID), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 308)
    - Committees (Senate): Academic Affairs, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 309)
    - Committees (Senate): Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - Condolences, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 311)
    - Congratulations, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 312)
    - Council of Presidents (COP), Jan.-Apr. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 313)
    - COP, May-Aug. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 314)
    - COP, Sept.-Dec. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 315)
    - Miscellaneous "D", 1994 (Box 11, Folder 316)
    - Degrees, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 317)
    - Development: Campaign Project, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 318)
    - Development: Foundation, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 319)
    - Development: Gift Reports, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 320)
    - Development: Office, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 321)
    - Development: Letters Signed by Sam Smith (1), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 322)
    - Development: Letters Signed by SHS (2), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 323)
    - Development: Letters Signed by SHS (3), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 324)
    - Development: President's Associates, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 325)
    - Distance Education, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 326)
    - Dow, Lohnes, and Albertson, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 327)
    - Miscellaneous "E", 1994 (Box 11, Folder 328)
    - Education, College of, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 329)
    - Engineers and Architecture, College of, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - E-I
    - Executive Budget Committee, Jan.-June 1994 (Box 12, Folder 331)
    - Executive Budget Committee, July-Dec. 1994 (Box 12, Folder 332)
    - Extended University Services, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 333)
    - Exxon, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 334)
    - Miscellaneous "F", 1994 (Box 12, Folder 335)
    - Facilities Dedication and Naming Ceremonies, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 336)
    - Facilities Planning, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 337)
    - Faculty, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 338)
    - Faculty Manual, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 339)
    - Faculty: Senate (1), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 340)
    - Faculty: Senate (2), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 341)
    - Federal Relations, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 342)
    - Financial Aid, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 343)
    - Faculty Status, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 344)
    - Financial Reports, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 345)
    - Floor Plans (French Ad), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 346)
    - Foley, Tom - Foley Institute, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 347)
    - Football, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 348)
    - Forward Washington, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 349)
    - Miscellaneous "G", 1994 (Box 12, Folder 350)
    - Governmental Relations, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 351)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Association, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 352)
    - Graduate School: OGRD, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 353)
    - Miscellaneous "H", 1994 (Box 12, Folder 354)
    - Honors Program, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 355)
    - Honor Roll, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 356)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Administration (HRA), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 357)
    - Human Relations and Resources, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 358)
    - Miscellaneous "I", 1994 (Box 12, Folder 359)
    - India: Jaipur, Bikaner, Delhi- CID Rajasthan Project, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 360)
    - Italy, Rome - First Global Conference on Life - Long Learning, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 361)
    - Idaho Research Foundation, Inc., 1994 (Box 12, Folder 362)
    - Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - I-N
    - Inaugurations, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 364)
    - International Programs Development Office, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 365)
    - Invitations, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 366)
    - Miscellaneous "J", 1994 (Box 13, Folder 367)
    - Japan, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 368)
    - Joint Center for Higher Education, Spokane, Jan.-June 1994 (Box 13, Folder 369)
    - JCHE, July-Sept. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 370)
    - JCHE, Oct.-Dec. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 371)
    - Miscellaneous "K", 1994 (Box 13, Folder 372)
    - Miscellaneous "L", 1994 (Box 13, Folder 373)
    - Kellogg Foundation, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 374)